affilistore.com 2007-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Affiliate Marketing Websites | AffiliStore

**PRIVACY POLICY AND CONSENT TO USE OF DATA  
**IMPORTANT: BY SUBMITTING DATA TO US AND/OR USING OUR WEB SITE YOU GIVE YOUR CONSENT THAT ALL PERSONAL DATA THAT YOU SUBMIT MAY BE PROCESSED BY US IN THE MANNER AND FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY.

**Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy describes AffiliStore's current policies and practices with regard to Personal Data collected by us manually or through this web site (“Web Site”). The term “Personal Data” refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address. 

**Notification of changes to this Policy**  
We are continually improving and adding new functionality and features to this Web Site and improving and adding to our existing services. Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law and the changing nature of technology, our data practices will change from time to time. If and when our data practices change, we will (as soon as practicable) post the changes on our Web Site to notify you of the changes. We encourage you to check this page frequently. 

**Collection of Personal Data including e-mail addresses**  
We will collect and store the information you give us. You may use this Web Site to register to receive additional information or services from us. When you register, we ask you for contact information like your name, postal address and e-mail address. 

**Use of Personal Data  
**We process your Personal Data only for specific and limited purposes. We ask only for data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes. Some of these purposes include the following:-

We may contact you occasionally to inform you of new services we will be providing, or events or articles we think will be of interest to you.   
We may send you requested information and related material.   
We will use your Personal Data to provide our services.  
We may use your Personal Data internally to help us improve our services and to help resolve any problems. 

**Opt-out choice  
**If you do not wish to receive information from us and want to be removed from our standard mailing list, please change your forums profile or click the unsubscribe link which can be found at the bottom of every email we send.

**Anonymous data collected through this Web Site**  
In addition to the information we collect as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our Web Site. For example, we use technology to track which pages of our Web Site our visitors view. We also use technology to determine which Web browsers our visitors use. This technology does not identify you personally, it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our Web Site. 

Our Web Site contains hyperlinks to other pages on our Web Site. We use technology to track how often these links are used and which pages on our Web Site our visitors choose to view. Again this technology does not identify you personally – it simply enables us to compile statistics about the use of these hyperlinks. 

We use this anonymous data to improve the content and functionality of this Web Site and our e-mail updates, to better understand our clients and markets, and to improve our services.

**Cookies**  
In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may in the future use temporary “cookies” that collect the first level domain name of the user (for example, if your e-mail address is “john@example.com,” the cookie collects the “example.com” portion of your e-mail address) and the date and time you accessed this Web Site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not. 

We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as determining how many of our visitors are from outside of the UK. 

We may also perform IP lookups to determine which domain you are coming from (i.e: aol.com, yourcompany.com) to more accurately gauge our users' demographics. 

**Disclosure of your Personal Data**  
We do not share, sell or distribute your Personal Data with unrelated third parties, except under these limited circumstances:-

Personal Data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for us for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. 

We may share or transfer the information in our databases to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this Web Site, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganisation, dissolution or similar event.

We may share or transfer the information in our databases with third parties whose products and services we believe may be of interest and value to you. 

Where appropriate, before disclosing Personal Data to a third party, we contractually require the third party to take adequate precautions to protect that data and maintain confidentiality. 

**Data Integrity and Security**  
We strive to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of Personal Data in our databases and to protect the privacy and security of our databases. We keep your Personal Data only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or document retention requirements. 

**Data Access and Corrections**  
Upon receipt of your written request and enough information to permit us to identify your Personal Data, we will disclose to you the Personal Data we hold about you. We will also correct, amend or delete any Personal Data that is inaccurate and notify any third party recipients of the necessary changes. 

If you wish to access or correct your Personal Data, please contact us using the hyperlink on our navigation bar. We do not charge for complying with a correction request, however, for all other requests, we may charge a small fee to cover its costs. Requests to delete Personal Data are subject to any applicable legal and ethical reporting or document retention obligations imposed on us. 

**Link to other web sites**  
This Web Site contains hyperlinks to web sites that are not operated by us. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party web sites or any association with their operators. We do not control these web sites and are not responsible for their data or privacy practices. We urge you to review any privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any Personal Data about yourself. 

**Governing Law**  
This privacy policy forms part of our Web Site Terms & Conditions and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England. You agree to submit any dispute arising out of your use of this Web Site to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England. 

**Questions**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process your Personal Data, please contact us using the "Contact Us" navigation bar on this page.
